Thank you for watching our P&P
certification complete video course.
The lessons started with a class overview
and an immense amount of foundational
concepts including traditional,
predictive, iterative, incremental,
agile and hybrid approaches.
We then covered each
of the knowledge areas
and also agile
considerations for each one.
With all of this information,
you have a solid
foundation for preparing for the P&P exam.
Continue to study the lessons referring to
your PMP for further clarification.
Be sure to answer the end of section
questions.
Going through the flashcards again,
do a random shuffle.
Then take one of the simulator tests,
treating it as if it were the real exam.
Plan to be there for the
fully allotted time, four
hours, and take one 10-minute
break halfway through.
When you're done with the simulated exam,
be sure to review every question.
This is truly key to understanding the
material thorough.
There are explanations to each question
and why the answer is the best one.
If you see areas of weakness, review the
lesson, lessons again.
Take the other simulated tests.
Repeat.
Once you're consistently
scoring at least 70 to
75%, you're ready to pay
for and schedule your exam.
Please connect with us on
LinkedIn and be sure to reach
out to us and let us know
when you pass the real exam.
and have attained your P&P certification.
We're very much looking forward to hearing
from you.